

MARK NOLAN

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Contact

Phone

(+353)851115357

Email

markjnolan00@gmail.com

Address

8 Beneavin Drive Glasnevin Dublin 11

Expertise

- Django
- React JS
- Python
- lava
- Full-Stack Development
- UI/UX
- lira
- Tailwind CSS
- GIT

Education

Dublin City University

Bachelor of Computer Science 2019 - 2023 Degree focusing on software development

Ardscoil Rís, Dublin

Leaving Certificate 2013 - 2019

About Me

Experienced graduate in computer science with 2 years of work experience within the technology industry. Effective communicator, delivering results under pressure and within tight deadlines. Adaptable team player and independent worker. Self-motivated, ambitious, and committed to excellence.

Experience

Hunch | 2022 - Present

Product Manager & Operations Executive

- Creating a clear and strategic plan for the project's development and success
- Working closely with stakeholders to understand and document the necessary features and functionality of the app
- Overseeing the project's development lifecycle, coordinating with developers to create a user-friendly app interface
- Hypercasual game development

Sportcaller | 2021 - 2022

Operations Executive

- Creating virtual games and quiz questions within tight timeframes for the app
- Ensuring smooth and accurate execution of each live round/game, adhering to clients' specific requests and needs
- Addressing client queries and effectively communicating their needs and preferences to the development team
- Providing support to product managers by overseeing their games during weekends and outside regular working hours.

Autobahn Roadhouse Pub | 2018 - 2022

Barman

- · Providing excellent customer service, taking orders and serving drinks promptly
- Maintain cleanliness and organisation of the bar area, restocking supplies as needed
- Handle cash transactions accurately, following cash handling procedures

Achievments

- Interviewed by Silicon Valley representatives at the prestigious Coder Dojo's Coolest Projects Awards for my outstanding 'Makey - Makey' project
- Successfully managing and resolving support issues for prominent clients, including Paddy Power, William Hill, and Coral
- Final year project, "HouseMate", designed to predict future house prices in Ireland on an interactive dashboard

References available upon request